TRIVIA_QUESTIONS = {
    "Football": {
        1: {"question":"Which nfl team became the first team to win six superbowls?",
            "answer":"Pittsburgh Steelers", "Steelers"},
        2: {"question":"Who holds the nfl record for most career passing yards?",
            "answer":"Chicago Bears", "Bears"},
        3: {"question":"What year did the first superbowl take place?",
            "answer":"1967"},
        4: {"question":"Which player is known for the famous immaculate reception?",
            "answer":"Franco Harris", "Harris"},
        5: {"question":"Which nfl franchise has the most regular season wins in franchise history?",
            "answer":"Chicago Bears", "Bears"}

    },
    "Soccer": {
        1: {"question":"Which country has won the most FIFA world cup titles?",
            "answer":"Brazil"},
        2: {"question":"Who is the all time leader scorer in UEFA Champions League History?",
            "answer":"Christiano Ronaldo", "Ronaldo"},
        3: {"question":"Which club does the famous stadium Camp Nou belong to?",
            "answer":"FC Barcalona"},
        4: {"question":"Which club does the famous stadium Camp Nou belong to?",
            "answer":["US", "Canada", "Mexico"]},
        5: {"question":"Who one the Ballon d'Or in 2021?",
            "answer": "Lionel Messi", "Messi"},
    },
    "Baseball": {
        1: {"question":"Which MLB team has the most world series championships?",
            "answer":"New York Yankees", "Yankees"},
        2: {"question":"Who holds the record for most career home runs",
            "answer":"Barry Bonds", "Bonds"},
        3: {"question":"Which pitcher threw a perfect game in the 2010 post season?",
            "answer":"Roy Halladay", "Halladay"},
        4: {"question":"What year was the first world series?",
            "answer":"1903"},
        5: {"question":"Which MLB team is known as the big red machine?",
            "answer":"Cinncinati Reds", "Reds"},
    },
    "Basketball": {
        1: {"question":"Which NBA player holds the record for most career points?",
            "answer":"Lebron James", "James"},
        2: {"question":"Who was the first NBA player to win the MVP award unanimously?",
            "answer":"Stephen Curry", "Curry"},
        3: {"question":"Which NBA franchise has won the most championships?",
            "answer":"Boston Celtics", "Celtics"},
        4: {"question":"Who was the only coach to win and ncaa and nba championship?",
            "answer":"Larry Brown", "Brown"},
        5:{"question":"Which team drafted Kobe Bryant?",
           "answer":"Charlotte Hornets", "Hornets"},
    }
}